export const questions = [
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "637e733998c089499ddf118d",
        },
        question:
            "An organization's core values, mission, and culture will establish its philosophical reason for being, or itsÂ Blank______",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        answer: ["foundation"],
    },

    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b382cc9b0a800089808c3",
        },
        answer: ["form\n\npossession"],
        question:
            "Which of the following are types of utility received by users of a product? (Select all that apply)",
        type: "multiple_select\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116844114",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116844114",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b383bc9b0a800089808c6",
        },
        answer: [
            "the ability to satisfy a need\n\nthe desire to satisfy a need",
        ],
        question:
            "In order for marketing to occur, both parties involved must have which two requirements regarding their needs?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116859828",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116859828",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3866c9b0a800089808de",
        },
        answer: [
            "Thousands of new products fail in the marketplace each year.",
        ],
        question:
            "Which statement supports the idea that good marketing is not an easy task?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116902757",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116902757",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b38cec9b0a800089808e9",
        },
        answer: ["Manufacturers could not keep up with customer demand."],
        question:
            "Which of the following is characteristic of marketing in the production era?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117006887",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117006887",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b38d8c9b0a800089808ed",
        },
        answer: ["the ability to buy, financially and otherwise"],
        question:
            "To be included in an organization's market, it is not enough for a customer just to want a product because it would satisfy unmet needs; a customer must also have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117016998",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117016998",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b38ffc9b0a800089808ff",
        },
        answer: ["products"],
        question:
            "Goods, services, and ideas can all be considered \nBlank\n______ in the right circumstances, when consumers exchange something of value for them to satisfy their needs.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117055564",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117055564",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3943c9b0a80008980919",
        },
        answer: [
            "An organization should try to achieve its own goals.\n\nAn organization should strive to satisfy the needs of consumers.",
        ],
        question:
            "Of the following, which two are principles contained in the marketing concept?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117123589",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117123589",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3e7561d3cd0008081057",
        },
        answer: ["the ability to buy, financially and otherwise"],
        question:
            "To be included in an organization's market, it is not enough for a customer just to want a product because it would satisfy unmet needs; a customer must also have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118453907",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118453907",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3ec261d3cd0008081064",
        },
        answer: [
            "delivering offerings\n\ncommunicating offerings\n\ncreating offerings",
        ],
        question:
            "Marketing is an activity that creates value for customers, clients, partners, and society at large. A firm does this by \nBlank\n______. (Select three answers)",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118530016",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118530016",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3f0a61d3cd000808106e",
        },
        answer: ["people with the desire and ability to buy a product"],
        question: "In marketing, a market is made up of \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118602948",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118602948",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b411861d3cd0008081074",
        },
        answer: ["be a more informed citizen when interacting with businesses"],
        question: "Studying marketing should help you to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119128803",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119128803",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b41c561d3cd0008081097",
        },
        answer: ["people with the desire and ability to buy a product"],
        question: "In marketing, a market is made up of \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119301281",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119301281",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b41c861d3cd000808109a",
        },
        answer: ["be a more informed citizen when interacting with businesses"],
        question: "Studying marketing should help you to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119304401",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119304401",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b41e061d3cd00080810a4",
        },
        answer: ["both the desire and ability to buy its products"],
        question:
            "To be considered a part of the firm's market, consumers must have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119328901",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119328901",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b44e49a3198000812d6b3",
        },
        answer: ["the ability to buy, financially and otherwise"],
        question:
            "To be included in an organization's market, it is not enough for a customer just to want a product because it would satisfy unmet needs; a customer must also have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671120100589",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671120100589",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b45119a3198000812d6b6",
        },
        answer: ["be a more informed citizen when interacting with businesses"],
        question: "Studying marketing should help you to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671120145189",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671120145189",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d175a665a650008170f18",
        },
        answer: [
            "They are passionate about the environment.\n\nThey are interested in memorable and personal experiences.\n\nThey are attracted to purposeful work.",
        ],
        question:
            "Select the three characteristics that are representative of Generation Y.",
        type: "multiple_select\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671239514021",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671239514021",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d19d714778d000995210a",
        },
        answer: ["The Federal Trade Commission"],
        question:
            "Advertising and promotion are regulated by which governmental body?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671240151541",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671240151541",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d1a5b14778d000995210d",
        },
        answer: [
            "tying arrangements\n\nrequirement contracts\n\nexclusive dealings\n\nexclusive territorial distributorships",
        ],
        question:
            "Select the four issues related to distribution that are monitored by the government.",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671240283941",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671240283941",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d1aae14778d0009952110",
        },
        answer: ["Generation X"],
        question:
            "What generational cohort consists of people born between 1965 and 1980?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671240366197",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671240366197",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d2cec868e6d0008f16dab",
        },
        answer: ["Generation Y"],
        question:
            "Which generational cohort's membership is known to be strong-willed, adept at creating work-life balance, and optimistic?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245036348",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245036348",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d2d05868e6d0008f16db2",
        },
        answer: [
            "issue a cease and desist order\n\norder corrective advertising",
        ],
        question:
            "What two actions can the FTC take regarding deceptive or misleading advertising and unfair business practices?",
        type: "multiple_select\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245061566",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245061566",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d2d14868e6d0008f16db6",
        },
        answer: [
            'often called the "baby bust" generation\n\nborn between 1965 and 1980\n\nsupportive of racial and ethnic diversity',
        ],
        question: "Select three characteristics that describe Generation X?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245076651",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245076651",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0870b756bc00080ae327",
        },
        answer: ["gross; discretionary"],
        question:
            "Nellie makes $10/hour and worked 100 hours, thus her \nBlank\n______ income was $1,000. Her employer had to take $150 out of her paycheck for taxes, and after she paid for rent and groceries, she only had $400 left. This amount represents Nellie's \nBlank\n______ income.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301232803",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301232803",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0964b756bc00080ae337",
        },
        answer: ["target"],
        question:
            "A \nBlank\n______ market is one or more specific groups of potential consumers toward which an organization directs its marketing program.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301476015",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301476015",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e097fb756bc00080ae349",
        },
        answer: ["sometimes purchase with the intention of reselling"],
        question: "Organizational buyers \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301503290",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301503290",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e09e6b756bc00080ae359",
        },
        answer: ["controllable"],
        question:
            "The four Ps, or marketing mix, are the \nBlank\n______ set of activities that a firm uses to respond to the needs of its target market.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301606244",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301606244",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0a66b756bc00080ae361",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \ntttt\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 tttt , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \nok\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 ok , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301734018",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301734018",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0a9184ea6c000892acfb",
        },
        answer: ["controllable"],
        question:
            "Especially when compared with the environmental forces, the elements of the marketing mix can be viewed as \nBlank\n______ factors impacting the organization.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301777533",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301777533",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0c5db756bc00080ae375",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \ntest\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 test , Incorrect Unavailable\n \ntest2\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 test2 , Incorrect Unavailable\n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302237312",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302237312",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0c81b756bc00080ae377",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \ntest\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 test , Incorrect Unavailable\n \ntest2\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 test2 , Incorrect Unavailable\n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302273233",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302273233",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e1274b756bc00080ae3b9",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \nwedw\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 wedw , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \nwed\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 wed , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671303796632",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671303796632",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e1331b756bc00080ae3da",
        },
        answer: [
            "manufacturers were able to produce more than consumers were able to buy",
        ],
        question: "During the sales-oriented era \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671303985036",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671303985036",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e13de7a7c28000886dbee",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \nhuihui\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 huihui , Incorrect Unavailable\n \nuhuihi\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 uhuihi , Incorrect Unavailable\n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304158252",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304158252",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e13e6b756bc00080ae3df",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \nijpjpj\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 ijpjpj , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \npojpj\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 pojpj , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304166225",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304166225",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e14b37a7c28000886dbf3",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \njb\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 jb , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \nuguj\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 uguj , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304371444",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304371444",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e14c57a7c28000886dbfe",
        },
        answer: ["be a more informed citizen when interacting with businesses"],
        question: "Studying marketing should help you to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304389159",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304389159",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e167f7a7c28000886dc1a",
        },
        answer: [
            "manufacturers were able to produce more than consumers were able to buy",
        ],
        question: "During the sales-oriented era \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304831241",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304831241",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e169bb756bc00080ae3f6",
        },
        answer: ["excess inventory"],
        question:
            "During the sales-oriented era, firms found an answer to their \nBlank\n______ by adding salespeople to find new buyers.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304859860",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304859860",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0a983acb1da0008a9abb2",
        },
        answer: ["changing beliefs about certain attributes"],
        question:
            "There are three approaches used by marketers to change consumers' attitude. They are changing the perceived importance of attributes, adding new attributes to the product, and \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "b6794ef4-a150-5a92-bff6-aaaaeec284a0",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671473539686",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671473539686",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0adb2950d380008bceac9",
        },
        answer: ["cognitive learning"],
        question:
            "The process by which a firm attempts to have the consumer associate two ideas such as a drug and headache relief is called \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "9699c844-9f03-54fc-a68a-00e27aaf9a5f",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474610173",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474610173",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0adb8950d380008bceace",
        },
        answer: ["postpurchase"],
        question:
            "The final step, and a very important element in retaining and building a loyal customer base, in the purchase decision process is the \nBlank\n______ behavior stage.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "012e7558-2fe8-5f6e-a31c-83ee2b3050c1",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474616883",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474616883",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0ae10950d380008bceae2",
        },
        answer: ["prestige\n\nstatus\n\nself-respect"],
        question:
            "Select the three needs that would be classified as personal needs.",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "3d22776d-1896-52d3-a0b3-c4a268175406",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474704492",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474704492",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0ae6a950d380008bceafd",
        },
        answer: ["actual and ideal"],
        question:
            "Marketers recognize that people have which two types of self-concepts?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "61ca8f76-6ae0-503b-a578-27d5868738df",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474794905",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474794905",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "637e733998c089499ddf118a",
        },
        question:
            "A large health products manufacturer has three distinct divisions: first aid products, oral care products, and foot care products. Each of these divisions has a specific strategy to target a specific market. These three divisions are referred to asÂ Blank______",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        answer: ["strategic business units (SBUs)"],
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b384fc9b0a800089808d0",
        },
        answer: ["both the desire and ability to buy its products"],
        question:
            "To be considered a part of the firm's market, consumers must have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116879029",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116879029",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3854c9b0a800089808d5",
        },
        answer: ["Best service\n\nBest product\n\nBest price"],
        question:
            "Many successful firms deliver outstanding customer value using which three strategies?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116884401",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671116884401",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b38edc9b0a800089808f2",
        },
        answer: ["output"],
        question:
            "Manufacturers in the production-oriented marketing era were concerned with increasing \nBlank\n______, not with satisfying needs of consumers.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117037861",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117037861",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b38f0c9b0a800089808f5",
        },
        answer: [
            "Organizations strive to achieve the organization's goals.\n\nOrganizations try to satisfy consumers' needs.",
        ],
        question:
            "Which two of the following are characteristic of the marketing concept era?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117040995",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117040995",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b391cc9b0a80008980909",
        },
        answer: ["the marketing concept"],
        question:
            "The idea that a company should attempt to satisfy its customers' needs while at the same time try to achieve its own objectives is known as \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117084938",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117084938",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3920c9b0a8000898090c",
        },
        answer: [
            "A product's attributes satisfy consumer's needs.\n\nA product may be a good, a service, or an idea.",
        ],
        question:
            "Select the two items that are part of the definition of a product.",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117088820",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117088820",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3928c9b0a80008980912",
        },
        answer: ["the ability to buy, financially and otherwise"],
        question:
            "To be included in an organization's market, it is not enough for a customer just to want a product because it would satisfy unmet needs; a customer must also have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117096098",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117096098",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3946c9b0a8000898091b",
        },
        answer: [
            "An organization should try to achieve its own goals.\n\nAn organization should strive to satisfy the needs of consumers.",
        ],
        question:
            "Of the following, which two are principles contained in the marketing concept?",
        type: "multiple_select\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117126238",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117126238",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3949c9b0a8000898091e",
        },
        answer: ["organizational buyers"],
        question:
            "Manufacturers, wholesalers, retailers, service companies, nonprofit organizations, and government agencies that buy products and services for their own use or for resale are known as \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117129039",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117129039",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b39a4c9b0a80008980928",
        },
        answer: ["the marketing concept"],
        question:
            "The idea that a company should attempt to satisfy its customers' needs while at the same time try to achieve its own objectives is known as \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117220593",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117220593",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3a61c9b0a80008980930",
        },
        answer: ["both the desire and ability to buy its products"],
        question:
            "To be considered a part of the firm's market, consumers must have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117409229",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671117409229",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3ea861d3cd000808105f",
        },
        answer: [
            "It can make the individual a better consumer.\n\nIt can help the individual in career planning.\n\nIt can help the individual be a more informed citizen.",
        ],
        question:
            "How does having knowledge of marketing and its many applications help an individual? (Select all that apply)",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118504586",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118504586",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b3ec661d3cd0008081067",
        },
        answer: ["marketing mix"],
        question:
            "A marketing program integrates the \nBlank\n______ to provide a good, service, or idea to prospective buyers.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118534887",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671118534887",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b416561d3cd000808107e",
        },
        answer: ["a need; a want"],
        question:
            "Jacob is moving from Southern California to Minnesota and is in need of a winter coat. Jacob likes to look fashionable, so he is looking to get a designer coat even though it may not be the warmest option. In this scenario, a winter coat represents \nBlank\n______, and a designer coat represents \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119205824",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119205824",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b41bb61d3cd000808108d",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \nde2w\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 de2w , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \ndewd\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 dewd , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119291593",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671119291593",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b46254a87e400082a48a6",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \nqwsdqwd\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 qwsdqwd , Incorrect Unavailable\n \nqwdqw\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 qwdqw , Incorrect Unavailable\n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671120421820",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671120421820",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b48ac4a87e400082a48b5",
        },
        answer: ["the ability to buy, financially and otherwise"],
        question:
            "To be included in an organization's market, it is not enough for a customer just to want a product because it would satisfy unmet needs; a customer must also have \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121068823",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121068823",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b493619ec7d0009858b63",
        },
        answer: ["concentrating on the needs of some potential consumer"],
        question:
            "The primary interest of marketers when focusing on a target market is \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121206140",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121206140",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b494119ec7d0009858b66",
        },
        answer: ["a need; a want"],
        question:
            "Jacob is moving from Southern California to Minnesota and is in need of a winter coat. Jacob likes to look fashionable, so he is looking to get a designer coat even though it may not be the warmest option. In this scenario, a winter coat represents \nBlank\n______, and a designer coat represents \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121217671",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121217671",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639b495619ec7d0009858b72",
        },
        answer: ["target"],
        question:
            "A \nBlank\n______ market is one or more specific groups of potential consumers toward which an organization directs its marketing program.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121238008",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671121238008",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639cd1a1feb2a4000846a130",
        },
        answer: ["be a more informed citizen when interacting with businesses"],
        question: "Studying marketing should help you to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671221665871",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671221665871",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639cd3c2feb2a4000846a14b",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \nok\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 ok , Incorrect Unavailable\n \nhu\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 hu , Incorrect Unavailable\n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671222210702",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671222210702",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d1757665a650008170f16",
        },
        answer: [
            "They are passionate about the environment.\n\nThey are interested in memorable and personal experiences.\n\nThey are attracted to purposeful work.",
        ],
        question:
            "Select the three characteristics that are representative of Generation Y.",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671239511959",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671239511959",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d2d27868e6d0008f16dbf",
        },
        answer: ["FTC"],
        question:
            "The \nBlank\n______ might issue a cease and desist order or require corrective advertising as a response to deceptive business practices.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245095394",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245095394",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639d2d33868e6d0008f16dc3",
        },
        answer: ["achievement"],
        question:
            "Which value was important to consumers in the past but is a value that is less commonly held by consumers today?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245107175",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671245107175",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0608dc1fc00008d92e3e",
        },
        answer: ["equality\n\nself-help\n\npersonal control"],
        question: "Select three commonly held values for today's consumers.",
        type: "multiple_select\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671300616925",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671300616925",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e062bdc1fc00008d92e48",
        },
        answer: [
            "an electronic exchange environment with computer technologies and digitized offerings.",
        ],
        question: "The marketspace is defined as \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671300651438",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671300651438",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0977b756bc00080ae33e",
        },
        answer: ["be a more informed citizen when interacting with businesses"],
        question: "Studying marketing should help you to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301495450",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301495450",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e097fb756bc00080ae34b",
        },
        answer: ["a need; a want"],
        question:
            "Jacob is moving from Southern California to Minnesota and is in need of a winter coat. Jacob likes to look fashionable, so he is looking to get a designer coat even though it may not be the warmest option. In this scenario, a winter coat represents \nBlank\n______, and a designer coat represents \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301503992",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301503992",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0a54b756bc00080ae35e",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \ntest\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 test , Incorrect Unavailable\n \ntest2\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 test2 , Incorrect Unavailable\n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301716231",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301716231",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0ab784ea6c000892ad08",
        },
        answer: ["a need; a want"],
        question:
            "Jacob is moving from Southern California to Minnesota and is in need of a winter coat. Jacob likes to look fashionable, so he is looking to get a designer coat even though it may not be the warmest option. In this scenario, a winter coat represents \nBlank\n______, and a designer coat represents \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301815090",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671301815090",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0baf84ea6c000892ad12",
        },
        answer: ["concentrating on the needs of some potential consumer"],
        question:
            "The primary interest of marketers when focusing on a target market is \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302063420",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302063420",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0bceb756bc00080ae363",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \nuijoj\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 uijoj , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \njojijo\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 jojijo , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302094433",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302094433",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0c44b756bc00080ae36f",
        },
        answer: ["controllable"],
        question:
            "Especially when compared with the environmental forces, the elements of the marketing mix can be viewed as \nBlank\n______ factors impacting the organization.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302212617",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302212617",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0c4ab756bc00080ae372",
        },
        answer: ["be a more informed citizen when interacting with businesses"],
        question: "Studying marketing should help you to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302218355",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302218355",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0c89b756bc00080ae37a",
        },
        answer: ["a need; a want"],
        question:
            "Jacob is moving from Southern California to Minnesota and is in need of a winter coat. Jacob likes to look fashionable, so he is looking to get a designer coat even though it may not be the warmest option. In this scenario, a winter coat represents \nBlank\n______, and a designer coat represents \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302281657",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302281657",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0ce2b756bc00080ae37f",
        },
        answer: [
            "They are largely beyond the control of marketers.\n\nSocial and economic forces are examples.",
        ],
        question: "Which two statements are true of environmental forces?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302370952",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302370952",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0cebb756bc00080ae381",
        },
        answer: [
            "They are largely beyond the control of marketers.\n\nSocial and economic forces are examples.",
        ],
        question: "Which two statements are true of environmental forces?",
        type: "multiple_select\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302379016",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302379016",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0d5cb756bc00080ae387",
        },
        answer: [
            "manufacturers were able to produce more than consumers were able to buy",
        ],
        question: "During the sales-oriented era \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302492180",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302492180",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e0d8fb756bc00080ae391",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \nyygii\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 yygii , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \nygugug\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 ygugug , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302543184",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671302543184",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e1314b756bc00080ae3d0",
        },
        answer: ["a need; a want"],
        question:
            "Jacob is moving from Southern California to Minnesota and is in need of a winter coat. Jacob likes to look fashionable, so he is looking to get a designer coat even though it may not be the warmest option. In this scenario, a winter coat represents \nBlank\n______, and a designer coat represents \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671303956508",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671303956508",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e13d8b756bc00080ae3dd",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \nhuihui\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 huihui , Incorrect Unavailable\n \nuhuihi\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 uhuihi , Incorrect Unavailable\n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304152044",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304152044",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e14b1b756bc00080ae3eb",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \njb\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 jb , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \nuguj\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 uguj , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304369470",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304369470",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e14bf7a7c28000886dbf9",
        },
        answer: ["excess inventory"],
        question:
            "During the sales-oriented era, firms found an answer to their \nBlank\n______ by adding salespeople to find new buyers.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304383659",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304383659",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e16867a7c28000886dc1f",
        },
        answer: [
            "It can help the individual be a more informed citizen.\n\nIt can make the individual a better consumer.\n\nIt can help the individual in career planning.",
        ],
        question:
            "How does having knowledge of marketing and its many applications help an individual? (Select all that apply)",
        type: "multiple_select\nyour_answer_incorrect",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304838121",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304838121",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e168db756bc00080ae3ed",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \njb\nBlank 1\nBlank 1 jb , Incorrect Unavailable\n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \nhv\nBlank 2\nBlank 2 hv , Incorrect Unavailable\n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304845943",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671304845943",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "639e24aaae16830ebc49cf87",
        },
        answer: ["red"],
        question: "what are your favorite colors",
        type: "multi_choice_multi_select",
        uuid: "9bebe63f-c837-42dc-96dd-d1c70a964ba4",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671308458852",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671308458852",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0a978acb1da0008a9aba3",
        },
        answer: ["personal"],
        question:
            "Arthur lost his watch and needed to buy a new one. This time, he decided to purchase a Rolex instead of a Timex watch because he felt that Rolex signaled his status better and was a more prestigious watch. His purchase fulfilled which needs?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "dcde09cb-4b55-54bb-9fc9-c04514d6a94e",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671473528466",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671473528466",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0aecd950d380008bceb0b",
        },
        answer: ["is consistent with your attitudes and beliefs"],
        question:
            "According to the concepts of selective exposure and selective comprehension, you are most likely to pay attention to and interpret information that \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "a6f41a9c-8536-5dc4-8b1e-af5e4a31f104",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474893945",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671474893945",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0af5f950d380008bceb2e",
        },
        answer: ["anxiety"],
        question:
            "Which of the following is most likely to be felt by a consumer experiencing perceived risk?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "339e3fbd-c31b-5fd3-965d-45cb6e1754e0",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671475039316",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671475039316",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0f3c4101f220009dbc8de",
        },
        answer: ["concentrating on the needs of some potential consumer"],
        question:
            "The primary interest of marketers when focusing on a target market is \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "6a9fcd33-1960-59f5-836f-7161f65ec97d",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671492548027",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671492548027",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a0f41c101f220009dbc8fe",
        },
        answer: ["True"],
        question:
            "True or false: The key to a marketing exchange is that both buyers and sellers trade things of value so that each is better off after the trade.",
        type: "true_or_false",
        uuid: "22fc0498-087a-51f0-a1f3-f55e0b4f1722",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671492636141",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671492636141",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1d84c45d8550008a210d0",
        },
        answer: ["regulatory"],
        question:
            "Environmental forces that shape the nature of an organization's actions include social, economic, technological, competitive, and \nBlank\n______ forces.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "b9f5a56f-25a0-5280-8367-2f750ec4fc32",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551052385",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551052385",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1d86245d8550008a210e2",
        },
        answer: ["to satisfy both consumer needs and wants"],
        question: "What is the objective of marketing?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "39cca77c-17dd-529d-93e4-fb852891a46b",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551074936",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551074936",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1d86d45d8550008a210ee",
        },
        answer: ["two or more parties"],
        question:
            "For marketing to occur, there must be \nBlank\n______ with unsatisfied needs.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "8d261619-9d3e-5e8f-bf6b-63a5e140d909",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551085483",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551085483",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1d87645d8550008a210f4",
        },
        answer: ["effective marketing research"],
        question:
            "Listening to your customers in order to develop a better product is an example of \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "226c6da3-4f00-5ad8-8e18-a1aa6e5d12e1",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551094751",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551094751",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1d9933fabbd000832ac71",
        },
        answer: ["place"],
        question:
            "Which of the four Ps represents the activities necessary to get a product to the customer where the customer wants it?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "4ce55c1a-cc41-59fd-8ece-cc5aaba044bf",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551379857",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551379857",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1d99a3fabbd000832ac79",
        },
        answer: ["promotion; place"],
        question:
            "TeaTime, a manufacturer of tea, has a new product that is currently only available in stores located in China. Knowing that it has customers around the world, TeaTime advertises the product on its Facebook page and will ship the product to customers via FedEx until the product is made available for purchase in other stores worldwide. In this scenario, Facebook serves as a \nBlank\n______ element and FedEx serves as a \nBlank\n______ element in TeaTime's marketing mix.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "ec3de696-700e-5606-ad04-e43e3c86f025",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551386939",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551386939",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1db663fabbd000832ac8a",
        },
        answer: ["customer value"],
        question:
            "Along with the price paid, benefits such as quality, convenience, on-time delivery, and both before-sale and after-sale service are evaluated by buyers to determine \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "b6663837-eb00-5404-a9e3-94307d4bf961",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551846061",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671551846061",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1f47c9a7e2f000809dc14",
        },
        answer: ["market"],
        question:
            "When a firm implements the marketing concept to consider customer needs in its strategy, it then is said to have a \nBlank\n______ orientation.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "aedad9f3-62d3-5975-9b90-4e0721f3f274",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558268738",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558268738",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1f5c3230c5f00083eca82",
        },
        answer: ["collecting information about customer needs"],
        question:
            "A market orientation requires firms to create customer value through \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "e614838c-57d4-5f78-adc3-0d129485ca54",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558595687",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558595687",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1f6d89a7e2f000809dc20",
        },
        answer: [
            "consumers who buy\n\nsociety as a whole\n\norganizations who sell",
        ],
        question:
            "Who benefits from effective marketing? (Select all that apply)",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "c4b5100d-dfb4-5ff4-a0a7-38b2e43e2dbd",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558872071",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558872071",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1f6de9a7e2f000809dc25",
        },
        answer: ["controllable"],
        question:
            "Especially when compared with the environmental forces, the elements of the marketing mix can be viewed as \nBlank\n______ factors impacting the organization.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "e22460a8-fe5e-588e-a0d8-d80247c5f031",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558878264",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671558878264",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1f7ac230c5f00083ecace",
        },
        answer: [
            "consideration of social and environmental consequences of their actions",
        ],
        question:
            "In addition to an emphasis on consumers' interests, new expectations of marketers now include \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "020c340d-98ad-56cd-8d1a-0004c335276a",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671559084406",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671559084406",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1f7c2230c5f00083ecad9",
        },
        answer: ["customers"],
        question:
            "Concepts like value and relationship marketing are important in designing an organization's marketing program because such a program is what connects the organization to its \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "90bac1e6-9b84-501c-8a40-e6ab48dd509c",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671559106298",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671559106298",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1f7c7230c5f00083ecae1",
        },
        answer: ["Every organization markets in some capacity."],
        question:
            "Which statement best describes who is involved in marketing?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "8ab1c5ee-9fbf-525c-957c-192bcd88b349",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671559111697",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671559111697",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a1fbb3e5746a00089408ab",
        },
        answer: ["Best product\n\nBest service\n\nBest price"],
        question:
            "Many successful firms deliver outstanding customer value using which three strategies?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "295517b5-efba-5918-b6e5-749ce35d01f3",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671560115536",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671560115536",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a2143ca973740008591dd3",
        },
        answer: ["possession\n\nform"],
        question:
            "Which of the following are types of utility received by users of a product? (Select all that apply)",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "edbd95b7-f0d1-5338-986d-ba31430d8337",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671566396656",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671566396656",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a33827a454be0008058ac1",
        },
        answer: ["FTC"],
        question:
            "The \nBlank\n______ might issue a cease and desist order or require corrective advertising as a response to deceptive business practices.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "2405ced7-03eb-500e-a124-8c3f66de8dda",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671641127367",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671641127367",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a3382da454be0008058ac9",
        },
        answer: ["more remote suburbs known as exurbs"],
        question:
            "Recently there has been a notable shift in US population from the suburbs to \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "fd4efbbe-f89c-55ab-9e4d-f99c1a0e3c24",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671641133373",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671641133373",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a338f7a454be0008058b09",
        },
        answer: ["Arizona"],
        question:
            "According to the most recent Census Bureau estimates, \nBlank\n______ is one of the states that has seen the fastest growth in population in the nation.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "a7226cd2-4b4f-5426-a6a6-789fb20c0796",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671641335376",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671641335376",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a3571f23339f00082a72a3",
        },
        answer: ["gross"],
        question:
            "The total amount of money made in one year by a person, household, or family unit is referred to as \nBlank\n______ income.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "c6436b53-bd60-5e32-a852-16365e204e05",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671649055672",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671649055672",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a3573a23339f00082a72a7",
        },
        answer: ["value"],
        question:
            "Using technology for the development of new products creates \nBlank\n______ for customers.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "e4a28cd9-5b19-5067-942b-0cbf537bfa7c",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671649082380",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671649082380",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a36fa9fc849a0008407a3d",
        },
        answer: [
            "the desire to satisfy a need\n\nthe ability to satisfy a need",
        ],
        question:
            "In order for marketing to occur, both parties involved must have which two requirements regarding their needs?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "5156022b-52ec-5087-afd8-d8cf601e6d31",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671655337566",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671655337566",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a36fb335ee990008ec0b3c",
        },
        answer: ["customers\n\nsociety at large\n\npartners"],
        question:
            "According to the AMA definition of marketing, who benefits from marketing activities?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "a68ce411-2ad1-5263-8d94-0652a305a0e7",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671655347822",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671655347822",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a37501adf07d000820aec3",
        },
        answer: ["Generation X"],
        question:
            "Those born during the 'baby bust' when the number of children born each year was declining are part of which generational cohort?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "16434f26-ec6f-51bb-ba4c-a22d2374f68e",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656705518",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656705518",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a3756a234e9c00081b3bda",
        },
        answer: ["echo-boomers"],
        question:
            "The Generation Y cohort is also referred to as the \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "1b3d06c6-9482-5798-891b-47fdf76772ca",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656810570",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656810570",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a37592234e9c00081b3be8",
        },
        answer: ["Generation Y"],
        question:
            "Blank\n______ is the generational cohort that includes Americans born between 1981 and 1996.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "67fc34f6-95b6-56b3-844e-15006673ad7b",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656850167",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656850167",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a37597234e9c00081b3bed",
        },
        answer: [
            "necessities like food, housing, clothing, and transportation",
        ],
        question: "Disposable income is used to pay for \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "b7c1e2c3-68bc-5e9b-8df4-01f9ed2d3096",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656855453",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656855453",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a3759a234e9c00081b3bf1",
        },
        answer: ["Consumerism"],
        question:
            "Blank\n______ is a movement to increase the influence, power, and rights of consumers in dealing with institutions.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "ba455d11-ead2-5362-81be-da73f3c059d8",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656858537",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656858537",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a375c4234e9c00081b3bfb",
        },
        answer: [
            "exclusive territorial distributorships\n\ntying arrangements\n\nexclusive dealings\n\nrequirement contracts",
        ],
        question:
            "Select the four issues related to distribution that are monitored by the government.",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "a33d21b6-3b93-5fb1-add6-e844b70c3d1c",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656900006",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671656900006",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a37663234e9c00081b3c0a",
        },
        answer: ["environmental scanning"],
        question:
            "The process of continually acquiring information on events occurring outside the organization to identify and interpret potential trends is called \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "fc7b5756-af6f-50f4-a006-c8d02696b70e",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671657059492",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671657059492",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a3767d234e9c00081b3c11",
        },
        answer: ["Regulatory\n\nEconomic\n\nSocial"],
        question:
            "When scanning the environment for trends, a company typically gathers information from five sources. Select three of those sources from the following list.",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "688b85fb-0d7e-541a-b412-ac6ce8a92422",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671657085703",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1671657085703",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a9cb8118102c00086861e0",
        },
        answer: ["management"],
        question:
            "While \nBlank\n______ establishes a firm's mission and objectives, the marketing department supports the goals by helping to provide satisfying products.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "c08a8a12-9f6d-589e-8b10-ca2cb5cf2091",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672072065790",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672072065790",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63a9f5a8e4e67ea95781fbf8",
        },
        answer: ["red"],
        question: "what are your favorite colors",
        type: "multi_choice_multi_select",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672082856838",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672082856838",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab39cf6b75170008e33686",
        },
        answer: ["ethical"],
        question:
            "Deciding whether to advertise to young children online represents a(n) \nBlank\n______ issue for a company.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "1c12ac31-6987-5b72-aaeb-e7468ce840d0",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672165839488",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672165839488",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab39f26b75170008e33690",
        },
        answer: [
            "Marketing isn't always easy; thousands of new products fail each year.",
        ],
        question: "Which of the following statements about marketing is TRUE?",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "5a9e7cdf-9a6b-553e-adc4-899ea66b45d9",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672165874572",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672165874572",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab7de8adab1c0008126381",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: marketing"],
        question:
            "The activity for creating, communicating, delivering, and exchanging offerings that have value for customers, clients, partners, and society at large is called \n.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183272968",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183272968",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab7e5523e4d10008a242a2",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: need\nBlank 2: want"],
        question:
            "A \n occurs when a person feels deprived of basic necessities; a \n is shaped by a person's knowledge, culture, and personality.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183381432",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183381432",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab7e6fadab1c000812638f",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: marketing"],
        question:
            "The activity for creating, communicating, delivering, and exchanging offerings that have value for customers, clients, partners, and society at large is called \n.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183407650",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183407650",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab7ec9adab1c00081263a2",
        },
        answer: ["focus on how the new product will benefit consumers"],
        question:
            "A marketing manager that plans new products to meet consumer needs should \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "43d97440-3d68-54d5-ad35-9c174c7e0b82",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183497024",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183497024",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab7ee6adab1c00081263b1",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: exchange"],
        question:
            "A marketing \n is the trade of things of value between a buyer and seller so that each is better off afterward.",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183526829",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672183526829",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab9875518c1800080779f6",
        },
        answer: ["age\n\nethnicity"],
        question: "Which two items are common demographic measures?",
        type: "multiple_select",
        uuid: "74c38adc-0902-5f82-b55f-6d78830d525d",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190069043",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190069043",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab9883518c1800080779fd",
        },
        answer: [
            "Pure competition\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nWheat, grains, and rice\n\nMonopolistic competition\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nCoffee, tea, soft drinks\n\nOligopoly\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nCell phone carriers\n\nMonopoly\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nWater, electricity, natural gas",
        ],
        question: "Match the form of competition with its correct example.",
        type: "matching",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190083215",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190083215",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab9896518c180008077a07",
        },
        answer: ["'minority'"],
        question:
            "Trends in the US population mean that it is likely that the term \nBlank\n______ as it is currently used will become obsolete.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "5e969309-7e2b-5575-b8bd-f1eb76d9e811",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190102635",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190102635",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ab98b4c101830008eb7775",
        },
        answer: ["more diverse"],
        question:
            "According to the latest US Census, the US population is becoming larger, older, and \nBlank\n______.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "c69ffa91-6001-5714-bcb8-ca978f74f848",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190132505",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672190132505",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ac35e3174b8d0008b77ef6",
        },
        answer: ["satisfy"],
        question:
            "Firms develop products and services with the understanding that their ultimate goal is to \nBlank\n______ their customers' needs.",
        type: "multiple_choice",
        uuid: "d32ede48-b014-5498-822f-48bef921e594",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672230371487",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672230371487",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ac3624174b8d0008b77f00",
        },
        answer: [
            "Form\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nThe production of the good or service.\n\nPlace\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nHaving the product available where consumers need it.\n\nTime\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nHaving the product available when needed.\n\nPossession\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nMaking an item easy to purchase.",
        ],
        question:
            "Match the following types of utility with the correct definition.",
        type: "matching",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672230436035",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672230436035",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ac452ae9009f0008c84b3a",
        },
        answer: [
            "Production era\n\nSales era\n\nMarketing concept era\n\nMarket orientation",
        ],
        question:
            "Put the four evolutionary stages in the correct historical order, with the oldest on the top and the newest on the bottom.",
        type: "ordering",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672234282617",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672234282617",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ac45a4e9009f0008c84b57",
        },
        answer: ["Blank 1: target\nBlank 2: market"],
        question:
            "A specific group of potential customers toward which an organization directs its marketing program is called a \n \n. (Enter one word in each blank.)",
        type: "fill_in_the_blank",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672234404011",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672234404011",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
    {
        _id: {
            $oid: "63ac5a338a7cbb0008085586",
        },
        answer: [
            "Social\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nIncreasing expectation for companies to make statements about and invest resources in cultural debates and social issues\n\nTechnological\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nThe Fourth Industrial Revolution\n\nCompetitive\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nA shifting focus from single transactions to creating ongoing relationships\n\nRegulatory\n\nmatches\nChoice\n\nChanging laws related to industries such as ride-sharing, cannabis, and healthcare will have an impact on marketing decisions related to advertising, pricing, and customer data collection",
        ],
        question:
            "Match each type of environmental force with an example of it.",
        type: "matching",
        uuid: "",
        createdAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672239667476",
            },
        },
        updatedAt: {
            $date: {
                $numberLong: "1672239667476",
            },
        },
        __v: 0,
    },
];
